[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a city in Oklahoma called Moon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most common method of child birth?", "correct_answer": "Vaginal", "incorrect_answers": ["Cesarean", "Water birth", "In Vitro Fertilization"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Zebras are related to rhinos.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how long is one astronomical unit (1 a.u.)?", "correct_answer": "149,597,000 km/ 92,955,266 miles", "incorrect_answers": ["174,000,000 km /108,118,587 miles", "8,000,000 km/ 4,970,969 miles", "878,000,000 km/ 545,563,907 miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following oceans is the worlds largest?", "correct_answer": "Pacific Ocean", "incorrect_answers": ["Indian Ocean", "Arctic Ocean", "Atlantic Ocean"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The does \u201ccheetah\u201d mean translated from Sanskrit?", "correct_answer": "Spotted One", "incorrect_answers": ["Fast", "Lightning", "Stealth cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sewing machine was invented in a dream.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following countries has the highest population?", "correct_answer": "Ukraine", "incorrect_answers": ["Uruguay", "Uganda", "Uzbekistan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the initial blueprint version of the 2004 movie The Passion Of The Christ?", "correct_answer": "The Passion", "incorrect_answers": ["Jesus", "The Son", "Christ"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the number of points outlined by president Woodrow Wilson for reconstructing a new Europe following World War I.", "correct_answer": "14", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "24", "27"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In ufology, what does the black triangle phenomenon refer to?", "correct_answer": "A type of triangular-shaped UFO", "incorrect_answers": ["Strange triangular marks on Mars surface", "Inexplicable black marks found on rock", "A triangular area of frequent UFO or other unusual phenomena sightings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first college in The Bronx, known as this today, was built in 1884.", "correct_answer": "Fordham University", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercy College", "Manhattan College", "Lehman College"]}]